https://portraitsofbritain.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Portraits of Britain View images by locationAbout the Artists & PrintsMounts & FramesDelivery and Returns Policy & Terms and ConditionsContact Us Twitter Facebook LinkedIn Google Plus CambrookeCompany Reg No: 1733651Privacy PolicyPrivacy matters to us here at Portraits of Britain. This page explains our approach to privacy on our site and how it affects you.Short versionWe collect anonymous statistics about your visit, like which of our pages you viewed.Some 3rd parties like Facebook and Twitter may know you visited this website, if you use their services. We can’t control them but we don’t believe this knowledge poses any threat to you.If you sign up with us we take great care to keep your information safe and we’ll never share it with others without your express permission.We never share your data with third parties except to help us deliver our own services.These are just the key points. If you need detail, keep reading.Measuring our visitorsWe measure visitors to our website using Google Analytics. This records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. All of that information is anonymous – so we don’t know who you are; just that somebody visited our site.The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better.You can learn more about Google Analytics or opt out if you wish.Facebook, Twitter and other social networksThese services provide social buttons and similar features which we use on our website – such as the “Like” and “Tweet” buttons.To do so we embed code that they provide and we do not control ourselves. To function their buttons generally know if you’re logged in; for example Facebook use this to say “x of your friends like this”. We do not have any access to that information, nor can we control how those networks use it.Social networks therefore could know that you’re viewing this website, if you use their services (that isn’t to say they do, but their policies may change). You will need to check your privacy settings on those services in order to check or prevent this.Mailing listWe may send you email notifications regarding your service (such as invoices) or which you have specifically requested (such as newsletters or notifications when a report is completed). You have the ability to opt out of any of this communication at any time.We will never provide your personal information or email address to any third parties except where they are specifically employed to help deliver our own services, as detailed above.If you buy from usWhen you sign up for any of our services – paid or otherwise – we will record specific personal information about you, such as your name, postal address and email address.We will also collect and store information about your use of our services so as to improve them. For example, we keep a log of what features are being used at any time.We also log account and transaction history for accounting purposes, and to monitor our business activities.EmailsWe may send you email notifications regarding your service (such as invoices) or which you have specifically requested (such as newsletters or notifications when a report is completed). You have the ability to opt out of any of this communication at any time.We will never provide your personal information or email address to any third parties except where they are specifically employed to help deliver our own services, as detailed above.Online paymentWe use Stripe and Amazon to process all payments via the website. These payment gateways will therefore have access to your personal and payment information. When paying by card, Portraits of Britain themselves do not ever have any access to your card details.We share information with these companies only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.SecurityPortraits of Britain take many precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. These precautions include:Use of SSL encryption for sensitive dataHardware stored in secured datacentres behind firewallsAll access to information restricted by password and/or secure keyRestrictions to what information can be accessed via any locationWhilst we take great care to ensure any confidential information remains protected we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the Internet.Of course you are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. Nobody at Portraits of Britain will ever ask you for your password, so please don’t trust anybody asking you for it.Data BreachesIn case the worst happens and portraitsofbritain.co.uk suffers a breach which might compromise your personal information stored there, we will notify all customers via email and immediately enforce a change of password for all registered users.Accessing your dataIf you would like to check the data we hold and/or make changes to it, please see the Data Access Request page.Updates to this policyWe may update this privacy policy from time-to-time, particularly as technology changes. You can always check this page for the latest version. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.Any questions?If you have any questions about this privacy policy or your personal data, please write to us by email to sales@portraitsofbritain.co.uk or by post to Cambrooke Fine Art Publishers Ltd., Woodbrooke, Drewsteignton, Exeter EX6 6PZ, United Kingdom.View images by locationAvon (32)Bedfordshire & Northants (16)Berkshire (35)Buckinghamshire (28)Cambridgeshire (39)Channel Islands (17)Cheshire (24)Cornwall (37)Cumbria (12)Derbyshire (36)Devon (74)Dorset (33)Essex (26)Gloucestershire (47)Hampshire & Isle of Wight (65)Hereford & Worcestershire (24)Hertfordshire (22)Kent (75)Lancashire (17)Leicestershire (22)Lincolnshire (7)London & Middlesex (64)Manchester & Merseyside (21)Norfolk (21)Northumberland T&W, Co. Durham (28)Nottinghamshire (14)Oxfordshire (43)Scotland (29)Shropshire (26)Somerset (21)Staffordshire (13)Suffolk (34)Surrey (51)Sussex (68)Uncategorized (8)Wales (41)Warwickshire (21)West Midlands (14)Wiltshire (34)Yorkshire & Humberside (61)
